leancy.com 2014-02-14

# LEANCY | Privacy policy

This Privacy Policy explanation is developed in order to advise you on the following: what kind of information we collect from our web site visitors, why we do that and how we use the collected information. By using LEANCY's services you confirm that you have read this Privacy Policy and its paragraphs, understood them in their entirety, accepted their terms and agree to abide by them. This Privacy Policy may be modified or added to by LEANCY at its sole discretion and without further notice.

When you visit the LEANCY website, we collect the data sent by your computer, cell phone or another device, which you use to access the site. This data may include your IP address, the information about your device (including but not limited to its ID number, operating system, geographical location and the mobile network used), as well as general information available from our web server, such as your browser version, the data exchanged between our server and your device, and the list of pages of LEANCY's website you have viewed.

Once you have registered with us, we may also collect the following information:

  * — contact information: username, e-mail address, Skype ID and similar data;
  * — financial information: your account information in the payment systems you use.

Before you start using the services provided by LEANCY, we may ask you to provide certain additional information, which we will use for verification of your identity and/or billing address, or for the purposes of security and risk management, such as your date of birth, social security number, etc. We may also obtain the required information through authorized third parties such as credit bureaus and identity verification agencies.

When you use LEANCY's services, we collect information about your transactions and other activities on the LEANCY website. For security reasons, we may also collect information about your computer or another device used for accessing our website.

In order to ensure your protection from fraud and from loss of personal information, we may collect detailed information about how you use our services and interact with the LEANCY website. We may also collect additional information from other sources, for example, from your correspondence with our customer service.

Whe you visit the LEANCY website we or our partner intermediaries may place small data files called "cookies" onto your computer or another device you use for accessing our website. We use this technology with the following purposes:

  * — your member identification;
  * — personalization of your experience on the LEANCY website and the services offered to you;
  * — collecting information about your computer or another Internet-accessing device for fraud protection and risk management purposes.

When you visit the LEANCY website, we use both session-based and permanent cookies. Session cookies expire as soon as you sign out of your account or close the browser window. Permanent cookies will be stored on your computer until their specified expiration date or until you delete them.

We encrypt information contained in our cookies and therefore this information will be availavle only to us. You can disable cookies in your browser; however, by doing so you may interfere with your ability to use the LEANCY website. In most browsers, detailed instructions on blocking, deleting and disabling cookies are available in the Help section.

By "personal data" we understand the information that can be associated with a particular individual and used for identification purposes.

We do not regard anonymous information as personal data since it cannot be used for identifying a particular person.

We store and process your personal data on our servers located in the Netherlands and protect them using physical, programmatic and legal security means in compliance with the federal or local law. We use firewalls, data encryption and limited physical access to our servers and files, giving access rights only to those employees who need them for carrying out their direct professional responsibilities.

Our main purpose of collecting your information is to create the most possibly secure and efficient conditions for you to use LEANCY's services. We may use your personal data for the following:

  * — providing LEANCY's main services and technical support services to customers;
  * — transaction processing and notification;
  * — resolving issues, commission fees and troubleshooting;
  * — prevention of unauthorized or illegal operations;
  * — user experience personalization, statistics and LEANCY's services and website improvement considerations;
  * — verification of the information submitted by users.

You can view and/or modify your personal information on your profile settings page.

If you have any questions or issues concerning any paragpraph of this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact our customer service.
